The Black Ambulance
The black ambulance?
That's right. An ambulance blackened by soot.
The children taken away as its prey will have their souls stolen by the Grim Reaper,
never to be seen again.
Aah!! I'm so scared!
Is that what you wanted to hear? Then you'll need to try a better story!
Y-yeah, we know it's just a myth!
I've heard about it too.
A child was kidnapped by the black ambulance, and by the time he was found...
he had been turned into a mummy!
Aaah!
Stop it already, Anna!
Yeah! Come on, guys! Knock it off already!
It's not even a good story!
You were the one who asked!
I was just getting to the good part and you ruined it!
Yeah, right.
You guys need to grow up and stop telling those silly stories.
Jun...!
Come on. What's his deal?
He used to love stories about robots and ghosts... I wonder what's the matter?
Huh?
...a tire?
Waaugh!
W-Where did it come from??
Hm?
T-Theo?
Was that the...?!
I'm back!
Hey Jun, what's up?
What's going on?
I'm giving them a health checkup.
Sorry to say... but I'm faster.
I don't think so!
That's enough, you can stop! Stop!
Blue Cop is in tip-top shape.
I do feel better than ever.
Mega Trucker, you have a worn out damper in your knee.
Wait, what?
How can you tell?
Because, after ten years in this job, I can tell a lot just by the sound of things.
Whaddya mean? I need fixing? No way!
Uncle Edo's the best mechanic around. You can count on him, even if he is a bit of a grump.
Hey, I heard that...
Jun! Uncle Edo!
Quick, transform!
Aah, what a surprise, Anna! What brings you here?
It's an emergency! Theo has been kidnapped by the black ambulance!
What?!
You're the new kid, right?
Your name was... T...
Theo!
Oh, that's it! Theo!
My name's Jun. Come play with us!
No, I couldn't... I'm not good at sports...
Don't worry! No one starts out being good at something!
Are you awake now?
Sorry about that.
My tire slipped off earlier.
A-are you a talking ambulance?
Oh, pardon me. My apologies.
My name is Mega Ambler.
I'm a Metal Cardbot that looked after patients on planet Machina.
Ma-chi-na Me-tal Card-bot...?
Huh?
I saw it with my own two eyes!
The police car turned into a robot!
Could this be...
The black ambulance?
Just sounds like some urban legend to me.
I saw it with my very own eyes!
Hey, it's Theo...
Huh?!
A Metal Cardbot?!
What is it? Let me see!
Hey, hey! This is private!
You should respect his privacy, Anna!
Don't worry, you can leave the Theo case to me.
Uh, why don't you tell me more about that ambulance over here...
Blue Cop!
I knew I could count on Theo. He even sent a map!
So that means... they're a friend of yours?
Hang in there, Theo...
Jun...
Now, let me have a look at you.
Look... at me...?
Lie down and stay still.
Hm. No broken bones.
Alright, then.
Examination complete.
Wrapping things up...
What is going on?
Help me, Jun!
I told you to stay still!
Theo! Are you okay?!
Jun! Get me out of here!
What's this?
Mega Ambler! Step away from the child!
Did the police car just t-talk?
Are you also a Metal Cardbot?
What should we do?
Don't worry about Theo!
Alright.
There are more robots?
Who are you, then?
You don't know each other?
Mega Ambler is a notorious travelling doctor.
He goes around treating people without a license,
and charging them exorbitant fees.
But you can't deny my skills are the real deal!
Blue Cop!
Looks like you need my help again.
Mega Trucker?
There's no time to waste. Just say the word!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Just sit back and watch!
A-another one?
Theo, you gotta run!
Oh, o-okay!
Another patient?
Mega Trucker, Mega Power Tackle!
Mega Power Tackle!
Haha, that's not gonna work on me!
How'd ya like that? Mega Trucker power!
That was definitely powerful...
...however,
I found your weak spot!
Mega Trucker, watch out!
Huh?
What's going on here...?
You've been slacking on your maintenance.
You should have listened to Edo...
Are you alright?
Yes. And I'm ready to fight!
Got it. Mega Trucker, take back!
H-hold on!
Don't push yourself.
Blue Cop, setup!
Hm?
Broke out of your bandages, I see.
It's no use trying to find a weak spot.
I take thorough care of myself, unlike a certain someone.
I heard that!
Maybe so...
But, a weak spot can easily be made!
That's not what a doctor does!
Blue Cop, Burst Shot!
Burst... Shot!
Forceps Shock!
What's wrong? Should I have a look?
That didn't even leave a scratch.
Huh...?
That's not good.
Aah! What's wrong with your arm?!
I'll take care of your other arm too!
Blue Cop, watch out!
Blue Cop, can you move your shoulder?
Yes, I think it's okay.
Alright! I have an idea.
I let my guard down...
What are you doing?
So I just do this?
Trust me!
I'll make it so you can't move at all!
Now! Megabolt Punch!
Mega...bolt...
Punch!!
That's it!
Metal Cardbot... Change Up!
Mega Ambler... sealed!
Is your arm alright?
I think I'll need a little help from Edo.
Oh!
Theo! Are you okay?
Blue Cop... I can tell Theo, right? He's my best friend.
Jun!
Of course. If he's your friend.
Theo! There's something you need to know.
How's that?
That's much better!
And Blue Cop?
As good as new.
We have this one all cleaned up now, too.
I think you're all set now!
Theo. I have a favor to ask.
Don't worry! I promise I won't tell anyone about the Metal Cardbots.
I'm sorry I startled you earlier.
Let's be friends from now on.
I'd be happy to call you my friend, Mega Ambler!
Ah! That hurt!
Oops! I'm sorry!